Brandon Davis

Greensboro, North Carolina, United States

brancdavis@gmail.com

336.337.3270

linkedin.com/in/brandavis

Summary

A seasoned analytical thinker who emphasizes a fundamentals based approach to problem solving and process improvement. Having spent 10 years in Healthcare IT I udnerstand the importance of having bullet proof solutions.

I strive to develop solutions with a strong foundation that can then faciliate and expediate future ones. I find sticking to this approach allows for better scale and long term adoption of any given solution.

Experience



💸 Lead Application Developer

Cone Health

May 2022 - Present (6 months +)

Current leading the implemention of integrating Okta into the organization Mobile App and Epic MyChart.



Lead Application Analyst

Cone Health

Dec 2019 - May 2022 (2 years 6 months)

- Lead day to day operations for a team of 8 that administrates 45+ Applications including:
- *Nurse Call (Hill-Rom)
- *Philips (Guadian, Intellibridge Engine)
- *Badge Access Control (ProWatch)
- *Security Camera System (MileStone)
- *Fetal Monitoring (Obix)
- Create and optimize support standards to meet organizational KPIs
- Track team resource allocations to systems
- Design and lead implementations of integrations, upgrades, and new systems
- Meet with business units and provide solutions based on their requirements
- Provide data analysis to aid business unit decision making
- Provide project management for small to medium size projects (1-5 teams)

Other Duties:

- Lead the department's policies and procedures committee
- Trainer in the IT Customer Service training program



Application Analyst II

Cone Health

May 2015 - Dec 2019 (4 years 8 months)

Liaison between IT and other Departments in the design, installation, and support of their related application systems.

- Plan and coordinate software upgrades using Change Control.
- Document best practices for support and maintenance
- Communicate changes in IT Infrastructure to affected stakeholders
- Work with vendors to optimize user workflows and resolve application related issues
- Coordinate regular maintenance for all assigned systems
- Re-mediate identified security vulnerabilities in systems.
- Scripting activities such as error checks and file maintenance.
- Design and implement system architecture



PC Systems Specialist

Cone Health

Feb 2013 - May 2015 (2 years 4 months)

- Hardware and software troubleshooting (on-site and remote)
- Hardware replacements
- Software installation
- Support ticket prioritization
- Supported 15 outpatient practices in the Reidsville and Greensboro areas

Education



University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Boot Camp, Full Stack Development Jun 2022 - Nov 2022



Ashland University

BS, Computer Science, Computer Art & Graphics Programming 2007 - 2012

Licenses & Certifications



IT Information Library Foundations Certification (ITIL) - PeopleCert

Skills

ServiceNow • JavaScript • Process Automation • Vendor Management • Customer Service • Troubleshooting • Project Management • Server Administration • Software Installation • Higher Education